<!-- Plugin Configuration File. Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <!-- Unique identifier of the plugin. It should be FQN. It cannot be changed between the plugin versions. -->
    <id>com.pan.SvgEasy</id>

    <!-- Public plugin name should be written in Title Case.
         Guidelines: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/marketplace/plugin-overview-page.html#plugin-name -->
    <name>SvgEasy</name>

    <!-- A displayed Vendor name or Organization ID displayed on the Plugins Page. -->
    <vendor url="https://github.com/robertpanvip/SvgEazy.git">PAN</vendor>

    <!-- Description of the plugin displayed on the Plugin Page and IDE Plugin Manager.
         Guidelines: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/marketplace/plugin-overview-page.html#plugin-description -->
    <description><![CDATA[
<p><strong>SVGEazy</strong> is an IntelliJ Platform plugin designed specifically for SVG files, delivering an intuitive and real-time code editing + visual preview experience.</p>

<p>Key Features:</p>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Side-by-Side Real-Time Preview</strong>: Left side uses the native IntelliJ editor with full XML/SVG syntax highlighting, code folding, and completion; right side provides high-fidelity real-time rendering powered by JCEF — what you edit is what you see.</li>
  <li><strong>Flexible Layout Switching</strong>: Quickly toggle between “Split View”, “Preview Only”, and “Editor Only” modes via right-click context menu to suit different workflows.</li>
  <li><strong>Seamless Theme Sync</strong>: Preview background perfectly matches the current IDEA theme (Light, Darcula, etc.), with optional subtle transparency for a more natural and comfortable look.</li>
  <li><strong>File Info at a Glance</strong>: Displays SVG dimensions (e.g., 256×156) and file size (e.g., 818 B) directly in the preview area for quick reference.</li>
  <li><strong>Native Experience</strong>: All interactions use standard IntelliJ Platform components — consistent style, no flickering, smooth performance.</li>
</ul>

<p>Whether you're an icon designer, front-end developer, or anyone who frequently works with SVG files, SVGEazy significantly boosts your productivity and visual feedback.</p>
]]></description>

    <!-- Product and plugin compatibility requirements.
         Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-compatibility.html -->
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>


    <!-- Extension points defined by the plugin.
         Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-extension-points.html -->
    <!-- 仅注册预览编辑器，不修改 FileType，不覆盖编辑功能 -->
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <fileEditorProvider implementation="com.pan.plugin.SvgPreviewEditorProvider"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>